Animation = {};
Animation.trivia = true;
Animation.giftDrop = 560;
Animation.video = { height: "128.5", width: "211.2", display: false };
Animation.special_gift = ['', 'star-new', 'snitch', 'box', 'bear'];
Animation.question_set = [
  {
    "question":"What is Dumbledore's sister's name?",
    "answers":["Anna", "Ariana", "Adriana", "Angelina"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question":"Who gives Harry the cloak of invisibilty in the philospher's stone?",
    "answers":["Sirius Black","Professor Snape", "Albus Dumbledore", "Mrs Weasley"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question":"What did Dumbledore leave in his will for Ron?",
    "answers":["Gryffindor's sword","A howler", "The Elder Wand", "Deluminator"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question":"What is the name of Filch's cat?",
    "answers":["Little Norbert","Mrs. Norris ", "Ms. Norris", "Ms. Norbert"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is name the publication by Xenophilius Lovegood?",
    "answers":["Quibbler","Daily Prophet", "Daily Planet", "Hogwarts Daily"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the school Victor Krum attended?",
    "answers":["Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry", "Durmstrang Institute", "Beauxbatons Academy of Magic", "Beauxtrix Academy of Magic"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Rons's mom?",
    "answers":["Molly Weasley", "Ginny Weasley", "Minnie Weasley", "Bella Weasley"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is Pansy Parkinson's house?",
    "answers":["Gryffindor", "Slytherin", "Ravenclaw", "Hufflepuff"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is not an Unforgivable Curse?",
    "answers":["Avada Kedavra", "Crucio", "Sectumsempra", "Imperio"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Lavender Brown call Ron?",
    "answers":["Ron Hon", "Won-won ", "Bon Bon", "Just Ron"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the wizards prison?",
    "answers":["Rock", "Quidditch", "Azkaban", "Hedwig"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Who dies in the graveyard the night Voldemort returns?",
    "answers":["Cedric Diggory", "Colin Creevey", "Peter Pettigrew", "Argus Filch"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Dobby wear?",
    "answers":["Pillow case", "Old bedsheet", "Draco's old clothes", "Lucious Malfoy's socks"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the half-blood prince?",
    "answers":["Dumbledore", "Ron Weasley", "Voldermort", "Snape"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape does Snape's patronus take?",
    "answers":["Stag", "Doe", "Rabbit", "Lion"],
    "correct": 1
  },
]
